emaxhealth.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy | EmaxHealth

eMaxHealth.com a Hareyan Publishing LLC company, respects your right to confidentiality and we are committed to protect your privacy.

Hareyan Publishing LLC EXTREMELY VALUES YOUR PRIVACY and respects your right to confidentiality.

Hareyan Publishing LLC gives links to third party websites for the information purpose of our visitors. eMaxHealth does not control third party privacy policies and cannot be held accountable for their content.

eMaxHealth discloses that third parties may be placing and reading cookies on our users' browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on eMaxHealth.com. For this reason below we provide options to our users for cookie management.

EmaxHealth does not collect any information about its visitors data except for email addresses when someone wants to comment under a story. No information is shared with third party unless required by law. 

Currently we are using Google Analytics to analyze the audience of the website and improve our content. No personal information is collected from Google Analytics. For further information on the privacy policy concerning Google Analytics, please go to [Google Analytics](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en).

### How to Customize Settings to Use Persistent Cookies

1\. In Internet Explorer, click Internet Options on the Tools menu, and then click the Security tab.  
2\. Click the Web content zone you want, and then click Custom Level.  
3\. Under Cookies, click the option you want to use under Allow cookies that are stored on your computer, click OK, and then click OK. 

### How to Customize Settings to Use Session Cookies

1\. In Internet Explorer, click Internet Options on the Tools menu, and then click the Security tab.  
2\. Click the Web content zone you want, and then click Custom Level.  
3\. Under Cookies, click the option you want under Allow Per-session Cookies (Not Stored), click OK, and then click OK.

### Privacy Policy Questions

Should you have any questions about the privacy policy of Hareyan Publishing LLC or with the privacy practice of eMaxHealth.com please contact us by using the Contact form or write to us:

**Hareyan Publishing LLC**  
4128 2nd St. NW  
Hickory, NC 28601  
Tel. 828 291-5884 or Email to info (at) emaxhealth (dot) com

**Last modified on January 10, 2012**
